Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
- Box: 66, Folder: 138, Publication (Box 66, Folder 138)
  - Item 1: Post-war wages, 1945; Publication (Box 66, Folder 138)
- Box: 66, Folder: 139, Publication (Box 66, Folder 139)
  - Item 1: Poverty has increased under "National" rule, 1935; Publication (Box 66, Folder 139)
- Box: 66, Folder: 140, Publication (Box 66, Folder 140)
  - Item 1: The principles of industrial administration, 1917; Publication (Box 66, Folder 140)
    Author: George Edson Toogood
- Box: 66, Folder: 141, Publication (Box 66, Folder 141)
  - Item 1: The problem of full employment, 1947; Publication (Box 66, Folder 141)
    Author: J. Winternitz
- Box: 66, Folder: 142, Publication (Box 66, Folder 142)
  - Item 1: Productivity: -for whom?, 1955; Publication (Box 66, Folder 142)
    Author: Les Cannon
- Box: 66, Folder: 143, Publication (Box 66, Folder 143)
  - Item 1: Professional workers, a speech, 1946; Publication (Box 66, Folder 143)
- Box: 66, Folder: 144, Publication (Box 66, Folder 144)
  - Item 1: The progress of the working classes in the last half century, 1884; Publication (Box 66, Folder 144)
    Author: Robert Giffen
- Box: 66, Folder: 145, Publication (Box 66, Folder 145)
  - Item 1: Proposed terms of settlement of the dispute in the coal mining industry, 28th June, 1921, Publication (Box 66, Folder 145)
    Author: Great Britain. Mines Dept.
- Box: 66, Folder: 146, Publication (Box 66, Folder 146)
  - Item 1: Protection at work: Phil Piratin's (Communist M.P ...) fight for safety of employment, 1949; Publication (Box 66, Folder 146)
    Author: Philip Piratin
- Box: 66, Folder: 147, Publication (Box 66, Folder 147)
  - Item 1: Protective clothing for women and girl workers employed in the factories and workshops, 1917; Publication (Box 66, Folder 147)
- Box: 66, Folder: 148, Publication (Box 66, Folder 148)
  - Item 1: The railway crisis, 1919; Publication (Box 66, Folder 148)
    Author: J.H. Thomas
- Box: 66, Folder: 149, Publication (Box 66, Folder 149)
  - Item 1: A railwayman in Russia, 1931; Publication (Box 66, Folder 149)
    Author: George Crombie
- Box: 66, Folder: 150, Publication (Box 66, Folder 150)
  - Item 1: The railways and the people, 1962; Publication (Box 66, Folder 150)
    Author: Tom Ahern
- Box: 66, Folder: 151, Publication (Box 66, Folder 151)
  - Item 1: The re-distribution of man-power in Great Britain following the Second Great War, 1953; Publication (Box 66, Folder 151)
    Author: Godfrey Herbert Ince
- Box: 66, Folder: 152, Publication (Box 66, Folder 152)
  - Item 1: The Women's Co-operative Guild, 1920; Publication (Box 66, Folder 152)
    Author: Women's Co-operative Guild
- Box: 66, Folder: 153, Publication (Box 66, Folder 153)
  - Item 1: Registry offices and public control: the powers and responsibilities of local authorities, 1908; Publication (Box 66, Folder 153)
    Author: National Union of Women Workers
- Box: 66, Folder: 154, Publication (Box 66, Folder 154)
  - Item 1: The relation of freedom and control in industry, 1943; Publication (Box 66, Folder 154)
    Author: Thomas Milton Heron
- Box: 66, Folder: 155, Publication (Box 66, Folder 155)
  - Item 1: The relationship between co-operation and trade unionism, 1892; Publication (Box 66, Folder 155)
    Author: Beatrice Webb
- Box: 66, Folder: 156, Publication (Box 66, Folder 156)
  - Item 1: The religious sanction of trade unionism, 1913; Publication (Box 66, Folder 156)
    Author: Charles Gore